Guide to the Carl E. Ladd Director of Extension papers,1924-1930.
Ladd, Carl E., Director of Extension papers, 1924-1930
- Federal, 1924-1925
  - Vegetable Gardening (Box 6, Folder 64)
  - County Club Agents (Box 6, Folder 65)
  - Forestry - Chautauqua Co. (Box 6, Folder 66)
  - Albany - Fulton (Box 6, Folder 67)
  - Genesee - Niagara (Box 6, Folder 68)
  - Oneida - mates (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - College Home Economics (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Smith, Ruby Green (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rensselaer, Martha Van (Box 7, Folder 5-7)
  - State Committee on New York State of Home Economics (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Correspondence, 1926-1927
  - A (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Morganthau, Henry - Eastman, E. R. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Agricultural Society (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - American Farm Economic Association (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Baldwin, C. H. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - B (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Boy Scouts (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Bradlee, Thomas (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Buffalo Slag Co. - I. J. Streeter (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - C (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Camp Fire Girls (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Chamber of Commerce, United States (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - D (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Dairymen's League News (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - E (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - F (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - G (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Genung, A. B. (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Getman, A. K. (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Gillett, R. L. (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Grange - State (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - G. L. F. Exchange (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - H (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Harrington, W. C. (Portland Cement Co.) (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Home Bureau Federation (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Hotels (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Howard, W. G. - Conservation Commission (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - J (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - K (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - L (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Land Grant College Association (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Mc (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - M (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Miscellaneous Letters Referred (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Applications and Recommendations for Positions (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Veterinary College - Dean V. A. Moore (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - N (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - New York Farm Bureau Federation (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - New York Farm Bureau Federation - E. V. Underwood (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Farm Bureau Federation (America) (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - New York Fruit Growers Cooperative Association (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - New York Potato Growers Cooperative Association (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - New York Food Marketing Research Council (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - New York Guernsey Breeders Association - J. H. Rikert (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - New York Seed Improvement Cooperative Association (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - New York Vegetable Growers Association (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - N (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - O (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - P (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Pyrke, B. A. (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - R (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Railroads (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Rural New Yorker - H. W. Collingwood (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - S (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Sheffield Farms Co. Producers (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - State Schools (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - T (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Telegrams (Box 7, Folder 68)
  - U-V (Box 7, Folder 69)
  - W-Z (Box 7, Folder 70)
- Subject matter, 1927-1928
  - Northeastern States Annual Extension Conference (Box 8, Folder 1-3)
  - Regional Conference (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Milk Conference (Box 8, Folder 5-6)
  - Annual Conference (Box 8, Folder 7-9)
  - Committee on Farm Practice and Animal Husbandry (Box 8, Folder 10-14)
  - Publications Committees (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Relations Committee - Extension Agents (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Extension Service News Board (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - College Seed Conference Board (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Exhibits (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - European Corn Borer (Box 8, Folder 20-22)
  - Farmers Week, 1928 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Farm Horse Situation in New York (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Income Tax Returns - Extension Agents (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Junior Field Days (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - 4-H Club Program Revision (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Capper-Ketcham Act (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Master Farmer Movement (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Muck Land Survey (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Radio (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Reforestation (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - State Fair (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Service Letters (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Winter Course (Box 8, Folder 35)
- College of Agriculture, 1927-1928
  - Farrand, Pres. (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Mann, Dean A. R. (Box 8, Folder 37-38)
  - Morrison, F. B. (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - Betten, Dr. Cornelius (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Thatcher, Dr. R. W. (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Appointments and Resignations (Counties) (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Appointments and Resignations (College) (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Business Office (College of Agriculture) (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - Purchasing Department (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Bostwick, C. D. (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Budget Correspondence (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Agricultural Economics and Farm Management (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Agronomy (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Animal Husbandry (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Dairy Industry (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - Entomology (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - Wheeler, R. H. (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Butts, G. S. (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Bates, E. A. (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - Robinson, M. (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - Peabody, G. E. (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - Witter, D. P. (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - Extension Service News (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Extension - Circular Letters - Montgomery Robinson (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Central Farm Bureau Office - J. Coryell (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Circular Letters - Farm Bureau - L. R. Simons (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - Junior Extension - W. J. Wright (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Publications - Bristow Adams (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Farm Practice (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Floriculture (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Forestry (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Plant Breeding (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Plant Pathology (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - State Poultry Tour (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Poultry Husbandry (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Pomology (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Rural Education (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Rural Engineering (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Rural Social Organization (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Vegetable Gardening (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Home Demonstration Agents (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - County Club Agents (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Questionnaire - Western Group (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - County Foresters (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - County Agricultural Agents (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - County Agricultural Agents - Nassau-Wyoming (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - College of Home Economics (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Rensselaer, Martha Van (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Mrs. Ruby G. (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Baker, H. J. - Questionnaire (Box 9, Folder 20-21)
  - State Education Department Survey (Box 9, Folder 22)
- Federal, 1927-1928
  - Secretary of Agriculture (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Bureau of Biological Survey - W. B. Bell (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Bureau of Education - Dr. Arthur Klein (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Bureau of Entomology - N. F. Howard (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Bureau of Agricultural Economics (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Warburton, W. A. (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Extension Service - General (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Graham, A. B. (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Ward, Florence E. (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Hochbaum, H. W. (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Smith, C. B. (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Payroll (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Annual Conference, 1928-29 (Box 9, Folder 35-36)
  - Northeastern States Conference, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Publications Committee (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Committee on Stabilization of New York City Milk Supply - E. V. Underwood (Box 9, Folder 39-41)
  - European Corn Borer Work (Box 9, Folder 42-43)
  - Farmers Week, 1929 (Box 9, Folder 44)
- Correspondence, 1927-1928
  - A (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - American Agriculturist (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - B (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - C (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - D (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - E (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - F (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Farm Bureau Federation (American) (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Federal Land Bank (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - G (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - G. L. F. Exchange (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - H (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Hotels (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - I (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - International Education Board (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - J (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - K (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - L (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Land Grant College Association (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - M (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Mc (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous Applications and Recommendations for Positions (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - N (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - National Farm and Loan Association (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - New York Farm Bureau Association (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - New York Home Bureau Federation (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - New York Agricultural Society (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - New York State Canners Association (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - New York Fruit Growers Cooperative Packing Association (Western) (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - New York Seed Improvement Cooperative Association - Bruce P. Jones (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - New York State Department of Education - A. K. Getman (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - New York State Department of Agriculture and Markets - A. B. Pyrke (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - New York State Breeder's Association (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - New York Cooperative Seed Potato Association (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - New York State Grange (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - New York State Hay and Grain Dealers Association (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Northern New York Independent Seed Potato Grower's Association (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - New York State Vegetable Growers Association (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - New York Cooperative Poultry Certification Association, Inc. (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Holstein Friesian Association (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - O (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - P (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - R (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Railroads (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Rural New Yorker - H. W. Collingwood (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - S (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Stannard, W. A. (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Sheffield Producers Cooperative Association (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - State Schools (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - T (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Telegrams (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - U-Z (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Subject matter, 1928-1929
  - County Home Demonstration Agents (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - County Club Agents (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - County Foresters (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Albany - Cortland (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Delaware - Livingston (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Rensselaer - Sullivan (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Tioga - Yates (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - College of Home Economics (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Rensselaer, Martha Van (Box 10, Folder 42-43)
  - Smith, Mrs. Ruby G. (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Meek, H. B. (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Master Farmer Contest (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Orientation Class - Extension Division (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Pasture Improvement (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Potato Program (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Extension Specialist Reports (Box 10, Folder 50-51)
  - State Education Department Questionnaire (Box 10, Folder 52-53)
  - Monroe - Otsego (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Dairy Cattle Study (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Questionnaire - Animal Parasites (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Radio (University Station) (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Rural Electrification (Box 10, Folder 58)
- Federal, 1928-1929
  - Forest Service (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Office of Cooperative Extension Work (Box 10, Folder 60-61)
  - Ward, Florence E. (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - Hochbaum, H. W. (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Wilson, M. C. (Box 10, Folder 64)
  - Use of Franking Privilege (Box 10, Folder 65)
  - Smith-Lever Inspection (Box 10, Folder 66)
- College of Agriculture, 1928-1929
  - Secretary, Office of the College of Agriculture (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Mann, A. R. (Box 11, Folder 2-4)
  - Administration - Cornelius Betten (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Gibson, A. W. (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Business Office (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Bostwick, B. D. (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Countryman (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Agricultural Experiment Station - Geneva (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Agricultural Library (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - College Departments - Miscellaneous (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Secretary (University) (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Warren, G. F. (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Agricultural and Economic Farm Management (Box 11, Folder 15-17)
  - Agronomy (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Animal Husbandry (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Dairy Industry (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Entomology (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Ladd, C. E. (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Miscellaneous (Administration) (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Wheeler, R. H. (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Robinson, Montgomery (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Taylor, C. A. (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Bates, E. A. (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Circular Letters - Extension (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Simons, L. R. (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Kelsey, L. D. (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Morris, F. B. (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Flausburg, E. A. (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Witter, D. P. (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Wright, W. J. (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Adams, Bristow (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Butts, George S. (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Forestry (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Plant Breeding (Box 11, Folder 39-40)
  - Plant Pathology (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Pomology (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Poultry Husbandry (Box 11, Folder 43-44)
  - Rural Education (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Rural Engineering (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Rural Social Organization (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Vegetable Gardening (Box 11, Folder 48)
- Correspondence, 1929-1930
  - A (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - American Agriculturist - Henry Morganthau, Jr. - E. R. Eastman (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - B (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - C (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - D (Box 11, Folder 53)
  - Dairymen's League Cooperative Association (Box 11, Folder 54-55)
  - E (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - England (Confidential) Miscellany (Box 11, Folder 57)
  - England - Dartington Hall - Leonard K. Elmhirst (Box 11, Folder 58)
  - England - Conference Report on Agricultural Economics in British Isles and Northern Europe (Box 11, Folder 59)
  - Outline Itinerary of W. I. Myers on Fellowship of International Education Board (Box 11, Folder 60)
  - F (Box 11, Folder 61)
  - Farm Bureau Federation, American (Box 11, Folder 62)
  - Federal Land Bank (Box 11, Folder 63)
  - G (Box 11, Folder 64)
  - G. L. F. (Box 11, Folder 65)
  - H (Box 11, Folder 66)
  - Halliday, C. W. (Box 11, Folder 67)
  - J (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - K (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - L (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Land Grant College Association (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - M (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Miscellaneous Applications and Recommendations for Positions (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - N (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - National Fertilizer Association (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - New York Agricultural Society (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - New York Home Bureau Federation (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - New York State Department of Education (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - New York Farm Bureau Federation (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - New York Department of Agriculture and Markets (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - New York Seed Improvement Cooperative Association (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - New York State Poultry Certification Association (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - New York State Vegetable Growers Association (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - New York State Grange (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - New York State Horticultural Society (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - New York State Bankers Association (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - New York State Canners Association (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - North Carolina (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - O (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - P-Q (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - R (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Railroads (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - S (Box 12, Folder 27-28)
  - Symons, T. B. - Director of Extension - Maryland (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Stannard, W. A. - Eastern Federation of Feed Merchants (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Sheffield Producers Cooperative Association, Inc. (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Sykes, Richard E. - St. Lawrence University (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - State Schools (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - T (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Telegrams (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - U-V (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Van Bomel, L. A. - Milk Conference Board (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Veterinary College (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - W (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Weeds and Weed Seeds (Box 12, Folder 40)
- College of Agriculture, 1929-1930
  - President Farrand (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - State College Council (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - University Secretary (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Office of the Comptroller (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Library (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Appointments and Resignations (College) (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Mann, A. R. (Box 12, Folder 47-48)
  - Mann, Dean A. R. (Box 12, Folder 49-51)
  - Betten, Dr. (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Agricultural Economics of Farm Management (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Hart, V. B. - M. C. Bond (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Agronomy (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Animal Husbandry (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Dairy Industry (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Administration - Extension (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Ladd, C. E. (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Robinson, Montgomery (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Wheeler, R. H. (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Taylor, C. A. (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Witter, D. P. (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Peabody, G. E. (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Circular Letters - Extension (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Flansburg, E. A. (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Kelsey, L. D. (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Morris, F. B. (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Entomology (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Wright, W. J. (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
  - Reynolds, J. A. (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Essick, Mildred R. - Mrs. Nancy M. Roman (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Adams, Bristow (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Butts, G. S. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Waugh, H. R. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Forestry (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Plant Breeding - Lewis, R. D. (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Plant Pathology (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Pomology (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Poultry Husbandry - James E. Rice (Box 13, Folder 14-16)
  - Rural Education (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Rural Engineering - B. B. Robb (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Rural Social Organization (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Vegetable Gardening (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Home Demonstration Agents (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - County Club Agents (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - County Foresters (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Albany - Livingston (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Madison - Yates (Box 13, Folder 25-26)
  - College of Home Economics (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Rensselaer, Martha Van (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Federal, 1929-1930
  - Bureau of Dairy Industry (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Office of Cooperative Extension Work (Box 13, Folder 30-33)
  - Capper - Ketcham Legislation (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Annual Conference (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Northeastern States Conference (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Agricultural Advisory Commission (Box 13, Folder 37-38)
  - Marketing Conference (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Governor's Conference on Milk Supplies for New York State Cities (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Publications Committee (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Stabilization of New York City Milk Supply (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Conference of Northeastern Committee (Box 13, Folder 43-45)
  - Survey for Report to Northeastern States Committees (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - Committee on Exhibits (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Committee on Extension Organization and Policy (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Farm and Home Week (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Gas Tax - Interpretation of (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - Legume Moculauts (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Near East Foundations (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Outlook Conference and General Outlook Material (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Extension Service Questionnaire (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Radio - W. E. A. I. (Box 13, Folder 55-56)
  - Survey Agricultural Resources (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Winter Short Courses (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Grange Lectures School (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Short Courses for Foreign Missionaries (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Summer School for Extension Workers (Box 13, Folder 61)
- Correspondence, 1929-1930
  - A (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - American Agriculturist - Henry Morganthau, Jr. - E. R. Eastman (Box 14, Folder 2-3)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - American Country Life Association (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - B (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Bailey, L. H. (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - C (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Cornellian Council (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - D (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Dairymen's League (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - E (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Eastern States Exposition (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - England (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - England - Dartington Hall (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - F (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Federal Land Bank (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - G (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - G. L. F. Exchange (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Geneva Experiment Station (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - H (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - I (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - J (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - K (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - L (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Land Grant College Association (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - M (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Manchester, A. M. (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Mount Hope Farm (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Miscellaneous applications and Recommendations for Positions (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - N (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - New York Farm Bureau Federation (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - New York Department of Agriculture and Markets (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - New York Home Bureau Federation (Box 14, Folder 34-35)
  - New York State Department of Education (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - New York State Grange (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - New York State Bankers Association (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - New York State Cooperative Poultry Certification Association (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Association Seed Improvement Cooperative Association (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - New York State Vegetable Growers Association (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - New York State Canners Association (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - O (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - P (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Pathe Company (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - R (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Railroads (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Roosevelt, Governor Franklin D. (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - S (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - State Schools (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Sheffield Producers Cooperative Association - C. W. Halliday (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - T (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - U (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - V (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Veterinary College (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - W (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - White, Pierrepont W. (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Weir, W. W. (Box 14, Folder 58)
- International Conference of Agricultural Economics
  - First Conference - Dartington Hall, England, Dec. 1928 - Sept. 1929 (Box 14, Folder 59-62)
  - Second Conference - Cornell University Speakers, Invitations, Programs, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 63-64)
  - Second Conference - Cornell University Publicity and Planning, Apr. - July 1930 (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Second Conference - Cornell University Budgets, Orders for Proceedings, Aug. - Sept. 1930 (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Second Conference - Cornell University Orders for Proceedings, Sept. - Oct. 1930 (Box 14, Folder 67-69)
  - Second Conference - Cornell University Travel and Program Arrangements, Aug. - Sept. 1930 (Box 14, Folder 70-71)
  - Correspondence re: Proceedings of First Conference, Dec. 1929 - Sept. 1930 (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Correspondence re: Proceedings of Second Conference, Mar. - Aug. 1930 (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Second Conference - Cornell University Radio Talks, Aug. 1930 (Box 14, Folder 74-75)